Guide to the Class of 1958, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Class of 1958, Yale College, records
1992-2008
RU 353
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
7.5
The materials consist of videotaped interviews with members of the Yale College Class of 1958 and a speech by Donald M. Caruthers given at their 50th Class reunion.
Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1958
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-A (YRG 10-A), Records of Yale College classes.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
Arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of videotaped interviews with members of the Yale College Class of 1958. Also includes a speech delivered by Donald Crothers at the 50th class reunion.
Videotapes; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1958; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae
- Speech by Donald M. Crothers delivered at the Class of 1958 50th Class reunion, 2008; Accession 2010-A-081; 0.02; (1 envelope) (Box 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
- Class of 1958 interviews [Videos recordings], circa 1992; Accession 1998-A-054
  - 1992 May 31
    - Mauro, Jean
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 1)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 1a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 1b)
    - Moore, Ed
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 1)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 1a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 1b)
    - Speare, Andy
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 1)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 1a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 1b)
  - Summer 1992
    - Jakaboski, Theodore P. (Box 85)
  - 1992 June 6-1992 June 9
    - Bauer, Tom
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 2)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 2a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 2b)
    - Dent, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 2)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 2a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 2b)
    - Goller, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 2)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 2a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 2b)
    - Hertzfeld, Harold
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 2)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 2a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 2b)
    - Hunt, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 2)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 2a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 2b)
    - Lontz, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 2)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 2a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 2b)
    - Strahan, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 2)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 2a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 2b)
  - 1992 June 13-1992 June 16
    - Birdsley, Ralph
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 3a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 3c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 3e)
    - Jaspan, Jon
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 3a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 3c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 3e)
    - Martin, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 3a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 3c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 3e)
    - Payne, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 3a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 3c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 3e)
    - Stack, William
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 3a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 3c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 3e)
    - Underhill, Dwight
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 3)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 3b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 3d)
  - 1992 June 16-1992 June 19
    - Kindred, Nick-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 4)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 4b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 4d)
    - Kreimer, Fred
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 4)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 4b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 4d)
    - Kudzma, David
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 4)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 4b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 4d)
    - Payne, Mary Ellen
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 4)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 4b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 4d)
    - Schlosser, Tom
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 4a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 4c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 4e)
  - 1992 June 20-1992 June 23
    - Burch, Ron
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 5)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 5a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 5b)
    - Caton, Donald
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 5)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 5a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 5b)
    - Goodyear, David
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 5)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 5a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 5b)
    - Kindred, Nick-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 5)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 5a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 5b)
    - Newburger, Kenneth-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 5)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 5a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 5b)
    - Newburger, Kenneth-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 5)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 5a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 5b)
    - Rathborne, Cocie-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 5)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 5a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 5b)
    - Tattersfield, Jim-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 5)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 5a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 5b)
  - 1992 June 23-1992 June 27
    - Callaway, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
    - Duff, Dan
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
    - McMurrey, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
    - Mourelatos, Alex-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
    - Newburger, Kenneth-Third interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
    - Rathborne, Cocie-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
    - Sellers, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
    - Seung, Thomas-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
    - Tattersfield, Jim-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
    - Underwood, David
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
    - Wells, Damon
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 6)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 6a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 6b)
  - 1992 June 27-1992 June 28
    - Boshnell, Ned
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 7)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 7a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 7b)
    - Farver, Cy
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 7)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 7a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 7b)
    - Mourelatos, Alex-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 7)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 7a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 7b)
    - Mourelatos, Alex-Third interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 7)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 7a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 7b)
    - Seung, Thomas-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 7)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 7a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 7b)
  - 1992 June 29-1992 July 4
    - Beckman, Jim
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 8)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 8a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 8b)
    - Carroll, Chris-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 8)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 8a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 8b)
    - Kaminsky, Neil-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 8)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 8a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 8b)
    - Kaminsky, Neil-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 8)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 8a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 8b)
    - Ryan, Terry
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 8)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 8a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 8b)
    - Uhlmann, Donald-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 8)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 8a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 8c)
  - 1992 July 4-1992 July 5
    - Carroll, Chris-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 9)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 9b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 9e)
    - Uhlmann, Donald-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 9)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 9b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 9e)
    - Uhlmann, Donald-Third interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 9)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 9b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 9d)
    - Uhlmann, Donald's family
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 9a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 9c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 9e)
    - Uhlmann, Eugene
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 9)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 9b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 9d)
  - 1992 July 5-1992 July 7
    - Blue, Linden-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 10)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 10b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 10d)
    - Molsberry, Jim-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 10a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 10c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 10e)
    - Norton, John-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 10a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 10c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 10e)
    - Norton, John-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 10a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 10c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 10e)
    - Wisz, Ralph
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 10)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 10b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 10d)
    - Uhlmann, Donald-Fourth interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 10)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 10b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 10d)
  - 1992 July 7-1992 July 10
    - Adnopoz, David-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 11)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 11a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 11b)
    - Blue, Linden-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 11)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 11a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 11b)
    - Bode, Fred
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 11)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 11a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 11b)
    - Molsberry, Jim-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 11)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 11a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 11b)
    - Norton, John-Third interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 11)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 11a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 11b)
    - Norton, John-Fourth interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 11)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 11a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 11b)
    - O'Mara, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 11)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 11a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 11b)
  - 1992 July 11-1992 July 13
    - Alexander, Rich
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 12)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 12a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 12b)
    - Bogan, Jack-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 12)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 12a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 12b)
    - Bragg, Spike
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 12)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 12a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 12b)
    - Gunn, Scott
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 12)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 12a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 12b)
    - Schoettle, Mike
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 12)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 12a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 12b)
  - 1992 July 9-1992 July 10
    - Adnopoz, David-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 13)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 13a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 13b)
    - Ault, Lee
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 13)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 13a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 13b)
    - Fitzgerald, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 13)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 13a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 13b)
    - Sargent, Tom-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 13)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 13a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 13b)
    - Sohigian, Ronald M.
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 13)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 13a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 13b)
    - Stoddard, Brandon
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 13)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 13a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 13b)
  - 1992 July 11
    - Chinn, Joe
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 14)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 14a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 14b)
    - Gerson, Gordon
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 14)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 14a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 14b)
    - Gilinsky, Richard
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 14)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 14a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 14b)
    - Saliba, Gil
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 14)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 14a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 14b)
    - Sargent, Tom-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 14)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 14a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 14b)
    - Scheyhing, Ernie
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 14)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 14a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 14b)
    - Taft, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 14)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 14a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 14b)
  - 1992 July 12-1992 July 14
    - Bogan, Jack-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 15)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 15a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 15b)
    - Schwettman, Alan
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 15)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 15a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 15b)
    - Stockdale, Frank
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 15)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 15a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 15b)
  - 1992 July 14-1992 July 15
    - Bass, Phil
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Dickson, Jim
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Hall, Zach
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Hellar, Grant
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Randall, Henry
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Richardson, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Sanderson, Ken
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Starratt, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Swidler, Tom
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Unobskey, Sidney-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Unobskey, Sidney-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
    - Yanowitz, Herb
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 16)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 16a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 16b)
  - 1992 July 20-1992 July 24
    - Holland, Maury
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 17)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 17a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 17b)
    - St. Laurent, Georges-First Interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 17)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 17a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 17b)
    - Stephenson, Leigh
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 17)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 17a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 17b)
    - Williams, Stuart
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 17)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 17a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 17b)
  - 1992 July 24-1992 July 29
    - Foote, Johnathan-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 18)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 18a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 18b)
    - Jenner, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 18)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 18a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 18b)
    - Wailes, Rusty
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 18)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 18a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 18b)
    - Winterbauer, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 18)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 18a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 18b)
  - 1992 July 25-1992 July 31
    - Cross, Rory
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 19)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 19a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 19b)
    - Sinel, Allen
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 19)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 19a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 19b)
  - 1992 July 29
    - Foote, Johnathan-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 20)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 20a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 20b)
    - Hickox, Barker-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 20)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 20a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 20b)
    - Hickox, Barker-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 20)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 20a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 20b)
    - Pendexter, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 20)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 20a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 20b)
  - 1992 July 29
    - Foote, Johnathan-Third interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 21)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 21a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 21b)
    - Foote, Johnathan-Fourth interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 21)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 21a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 21b)
    - Foote, Tim
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 21)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 21a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 21b)
  - 1992 July 29
    - Foote, Johnathan-Fifth interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 22)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 22a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 22b)
  - 1992 July 17-1992 July 20
    - Blatchford, Charley
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 23)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 23a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 23b)
    - Edwards, Jerome
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 23)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 23a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 23b)
    - Horton, Jack
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 23)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 23a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 23b)
    - Pool, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 23)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 23a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 23b)
    - Silberstein, Steve
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 23)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 23a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 23b)
    - St. Laurent, Georges-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 23)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 23a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 23b)
    - Zabriskie, Stewart
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 23)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 23a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 23b)
  - 1992 August 1-1992 August 5
    - Bascom, Perry
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 24)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 24a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 24b)
    - Chinnery, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 24)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 24a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 24b)
    - Connors, Edward
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 24)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 24a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 24b)
    - Duncan, H. Bruce
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 24)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 24a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 24b)
    - Joline, Lou
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 24)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 24a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 24b)
    - West, Marshall
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 24)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 24a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 24b)
    - Wimer, Frank
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 24)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 24a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 24b)
  - 1992 August 7-1992 August 9
    - Bales, Kent
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 25a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 25c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 25e)
    - Early, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 25)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 25b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 25d)
    - Opsahl, Bill-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 25a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 25c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 25e)
    - Tully, Ralph
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 25a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 25c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 25e)
  - 1992 August 9-1992 August 10
    - Lerner, Irving
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 26)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 26a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 26b)
    - Moore, David
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 26)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 26a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 26b)
    - Waterbury, David
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 26)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 26a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 26b)
  - 1992 August 10-1992 August 12
    - Carlson, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 27)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 27a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 27b)
    - Lubke, Arthur
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 27)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 27a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 27b)
    - Theis, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 27)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 27a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 27b)
  - 1992 August 12-1992 August 13
    - Bensinger, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 28)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 28a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 28b)
    - Porter, Morgan
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 28)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 28a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 28b)
    - Segil, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 28)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 28a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 28b)
    - Simonds, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 28)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 28a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 28b)
  - 1992 August 16-1992 August 23
    - Esserman, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 29)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 29a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 29b)
    - Rapp, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 29)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 29a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 29b)
  - 1992 August 19-1992 August 21
    - Covington, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 30)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 30a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 30b)
    - Cullinan, Keith
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 30)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 30a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 30b)
    - Dalton, Roger
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 30)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 30a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 30b)
    - Sachatello, Charlie
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 30)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 30a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 30b)
  - 1992 August 21-1992 August 24
    - Beiring, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 31)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 31a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 31b)
    - Hibbard, Russ
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 31)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 31a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 31b)
    - McCalmont, Sam
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 31)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 31a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 31b)
    - Reynolds, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 31)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 31a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 31b)
    - Wampler, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 31)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 31a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 31b)
  - 1992 August 24-1992 August 25
    - McMahon, Brian
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 32)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 32a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 32b)
    - Manoogian, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 32)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 32a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 32b)
  - 1992 August 26
    - Feinknopf, Mark
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 33)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 33a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 33b)
    - Holland, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 33)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 33a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 33b)
    - Preston, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 33)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 33a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 33b)
  - 1992 August 27-1992 August 28
    - Berger, Jack-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 34)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 34a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 34b)
    - Berger, Jack-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 34)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 34a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 34b)
    - Berger, Jack-Third interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 34)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 34a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 34b)
    - Colbert, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 34)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 34a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 34b)
    - Cutler, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 34)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 34a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 34b)
    - Eppes, Ben
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 34)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 34a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 34b)
    - Henkel, Pudge
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 34)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 34a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 34b)
    - Martin, Don
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 34)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 34a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 34b)
    - Rankin, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 34)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 34a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 34b)
  - 1992 August 13-1992 August 14
    - Baird, Lanny
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 35)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 35a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 35b)
    - Bartlett, Fred
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 35)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 35a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 35b)
    - Beatty, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 35)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 35a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 35b)
    - Burt, Henry
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 35)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 35a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 35b)
    - Crossman, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 35)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 35a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 35b)
    - MacCartney, Ron
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 35)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 35a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 35b)
  - 1992 August 15
    - Genskow, Jack
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 36)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 36a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 36b)
    - Wiliamson, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 36)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 36a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 36b)
  - 1992 September 8
    - Hand, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 37)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 37a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 37b)
    - Lee, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 37)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 37a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 37b)
    - Rogers, Joseph "Buck"
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 37)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 37a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 37b)
    - Straus, Tom
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 37)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 37a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 37b)
    - Warner, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 37)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 37a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 37b)
  - 1992 September 9-1992 September 10
    - Barhite, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 38)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 38a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 38b)
    - Grossman, Bruce
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 38)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 38a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 38b)
    - Hammond, Fred
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 38)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 38a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 38b)
    - Kwei, Tom
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 38)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 38a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 38b)
  - 1992 September 11-1992 September 12
    - Engel, Dick-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 39)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 39a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 39b)